练习 1-35：音节模式。为了练习准确的音高变化，请重复
Exercise 1-35, Syllable Patterns. In order to practice accurate pitch change, repeat
下面这一列。每个音节都算作一个音符。记住，
the following column. Each syllable will count as one musical note. Remember that
以元音或浊辅音结尾的词，会比以清辅音结尾的词更长。
words that end in a vowel or a voiced consonant will be longer than ones ending
A 列包含 la、cat、jump、box 等示例。
in an unvoiced consonant. Column A. la cat jump box law dog see plan la la a dog a
cat destroy a pen pretend your job, pea soup, la la, hot dog, icy, suitcase,
project, sunset, get one, do it, la la la, Bob's hot dog, Bob won't know, Sam's the
boss, Susie's nice, Bill went home, cats don't. Stocks can fall. School is fun. La
la la. A hot dog. I don't know. He's the boss. We cleaned up. In the bag. For a
while. I went home. We don't care. It's in March. La la la. A hot dog. don't know.
Jim killed it. Tomorrow. A fruit cake. The engine. A wine glass. Potato. Whatever. La
la la. Hot dog stand. I don't know. Analyze. Article. Dinner time. digital,
analog, cell structure, la la la la, spots a hot dog, Jim killed a snake, Joe doesn't
know, Nate bought a book, Al brought some ice, la la la la, it's a hot dog, he a
snake. He doesn't know. We came back in. He bought a book. La la la la. Bob likes
hot dogs. Anne eats pancakes. Cats eat fish bones. Bears are fuzzy. Planets
Rotate. La la la la. It's my hot dog. Imitation. Analytic. We like science. My
to-do list. La la la la. A hot dog stand. Jim killed a man. Analysis. Invisible. A
platypus. La la la la, permanently, demonstrated, category, office supplies,
educator. Column B, get, quick, choice, loss, law, goes, choose, lose, Bob Smith,
my car, some more, red tape and clothes consume my choice how's work wristwatch
textbook bookshelf sunshine placemat stapler modern modem worms eat dirt
inchworms inch pets need care Ed's too late Paul threw up wool can itch Birds
sing songs Spot has fleas Nick's a punk Make a cake He forgot Take a bath We're
too late. I love you Over here. What a jerk. How's your job? How'd it go? Who'd
you meet? percentage Advantage it's starting. Let's try it Financial. I
thought so. On Wednesday. In April. I love you. Let's tell him. Alphabet. Possible.
Show me one. Area. Punctuate. Emphasis. Syllable. Post-it note. Rolodex. Nate
needs a break. Ed took my car. Jill ate a steak. Spain's really far. Jake's in the
lake. Sam's in a bar. She asked for help. We took my car. We need a break. It's
really far. I love you too. They got away. Boys ring doorbells. Bill ate breakfast.
Guns are lethal. Inchworms bug me. Ragtops cost more. Salesmen sell things. An alarm
clock. I don't need one. Ring the doorbell. What's the matter? Introduction.
My report card. Potato chip. Whose turn is it? We worked on it. How tall are you?
Insanity. Ability. Supervisor. Window cleaner. Race car driver. January.
Progress report. Thingamajig. Column C. Stop. Which. Bit. Beat. Bid. Bead. Car.
Know. For you. Who knows. Cassette.
Ballet. Valid. Dog show. Want ad. Joe has 3. Bob has 8. Al jumped up. Glenn sat
down. Tom made lunch. Kids should play. Mom said no. Mars is red. Ned sells cars.
IBM. A good time. Use your head. How are you? We came home. On the bus. Engineer.
She fell down. They called back. You goofed up. Ohio. His football. They're
leaving. How are you? Emphatic. Dale planned it. You took it. External. A
bargain. Don't touch it. Phone number. Think about. Comfortable. Waiting for.
Pitiful. Everything. Orchestra. Ignorant. Rubbermaid. Max wants to know. Al's
kitchen floor. Bill's halfway there. Roses are red. Violets are blue. Candy is sweet.
And so are you. I want to know. The kitchen floor. We watch TV. She's We
played all day. Please show me how. Phil knows mailmen. Joe grew eggplants. Humpty
Dumpty. Hawks are vicious. Homework bores them. Mike can hear you. He said, light
bulb. What does box mean? Put your hands up. Where's the mailman? an assembly,
definition, what time is it, my phone number, let's eat something, how old are
you, untouchable, a maniac, lighthouse keeper, cough medicine, business meeting,
February, babysitter, dictionary.